nataliemaclean.com 2011-06-07

# NatDecants Privacy Policy | Natalie MacLean

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that **NatalieMacLean.com** ("Service Provider," "we" or "our") treats the information you provide while using www.nataliemaclean.com ("Website"). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. **Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy**. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website. 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

**I. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS**

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. 

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. 

**II. HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

Service Provider uses personally identifying information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our publications, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the publication. Similarly, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

If you do not wish to receive future communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail. If you've registered on any part of the Website, please use the mechanism on the Website that allows you to change or update your member preferences or information, if available, to keep all such date accurate and up-to-date. Otherwise, contact your Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below with your changes. 

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if you choose to purchase items through features on the Website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process. 

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website. 

While your personally identifying information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Service Provider, its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets. 

**III. COOKIES**

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information. 

If you don't want any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly. 

**IV. INFORMATION SECURITY AND NOTIFICATION**

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, Service Provider can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail (provided we have your e-mail address). 

**V. KIDS AND PARENTS**

This Website is not intended for use by anyone under the legal alcoholic drinking age. Further, no one under the legal alcoholic drinking age is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. 

**VI. PRIVACY POLICY COORDINATOR**

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as follows: Nat Decants, 303 Terry Fox Drive, Kanata, Ontario K2K 1J3 or or e-mail [natdecants@nataliemaclean.com](mailto:natdecants@nataliemaclean.com).
